Guide to the Records of the Office of Media Production RG.7.3.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Projects
  - President Oliva: French Legion of Honor Award (Reel 1-2), 1997 (Box 83, Folder Project 167)
  - LaGuardia Statue Dedication, 1994 (Box 83, Folder Project 168)
  - Secretary of Education Riley @ NYU (Reel 1-6), 1995 (Box 83, Folder Project 169)
  - Secretary of Education Riley @ NYU Master (Reel), 1995 (Box 83, Folder Project 169)
  - Wagner/Brussels Televideo Class (Reel 2-11), 1996 (Box 83, Folder Project 170)
  - International Student Film Festival (Reel 1-15), 1997 (Box 83, Folder Project 171)
  - Loeb Lecture Series: Arno Penzias of ATT(Reel 1-3), 1995 (Box 83, Folder Project 172)
  - Loeb Lecture Series: Arno Penzias of ATT Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 83, Folder Project 172)
  - International Student Film Festival (Reel 16-41), 1997 (Box 84, Folder Project 171)
  - Loeb Lecture Series: Allied Signal (Reel 1-3), 1995 (Box 84, Folder Project 173)
  - Loeb Lecture Series: Lawrence Bossidy, Allied Signal (Reel 1-3), 1995 (Box 84, Folder Project 173)
  - Loeb Lecture Series: Lawrence Bossidy, Allied Signal Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 84, Folder Project 173)
  - Musical Theater Hall of Fame 1995 (Reel 1-7, 11-16) (Box 84, Folder Project 174)
  - Musical Theater Hall of Fame 1995 Camera 3 (Reel 1-3) (Box 84, Folder Project 174)
  - NYU Basketball Goes to NCAA Playoffs (Reel 1), 1986 (Box 85, Folder Project 175)
  - Stern MBA Centennial Celebration (Reel 1-11, 13-16, 19-26, 30), 1999 (Box 85, Folder Project 176)
  - Stern MBA Centennial Celebration (Zip Disks 1-3), 1999 (Box 85, Folder Project 176)
  - Stern UG Parent's Weekend 1999 (Reel 1-9, 12) (Box 85, Folder Project 177)
  - Stern UG Parent's Weekend 1999 Master (Reel 1) (Box 85, Folder Project 177)
  - College of Dentistry Oral History (Reel 1-25), 1999 (Box 86, Folder Project 178)
  - Stern Undergraduate Professional Skills Workshop (Reel 1-11), 1999 (Box 86, Folder Project 180)
  - NYU Online (Reel 1-18), 1999 (Box 86, Folder Project 181)
  - NYU Online Master (Reel 1), 1999 (Box 86, Folder Project 181)
  - NYU Online (Reel 19-55), 1999 (Box 87, Folder Project 181)
  - Stern UG Pre-Commencement 2000 (Reel 1-16), 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder Project 182)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2000 (Reel 1- 10), 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder Project 183)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2000 Master (Reel 1), 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder Project 183)
  - Year 2000 Celebration (Reel 1-9), 1999 (Box 88, Folder Project 184)
  - America Reads Training Video (Reel 3, 5-7, 9-22, 24), 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder Project 185)
  - Stern UG Pre-Commencement Ceremony 1998 (Reel 1-4) (Box 88, Folder Project 186)
  - Meet the CEOs: Judy Harrison of the Monet Group (Reel 1-6), 1995 (Box 88, Folder Project 187)
  - Meet the CEOs: Judy Harrison of the Monet Group Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 88, Folder Project 187)
  - Reading Recovery Video (Reel 1-31), 1990-1994 (Box 89, Folder Project 188)
  - Stern UG Parents' Weekend (Reel 1-10), 1998 (Box 90, Folder Project 189)
  - Stern UG Pre-Commencement (Reel 5-8), 1997 (Box 90, Folder Project 190)
  - Stern MBA Commencement Video 1997 (Reel 1-9) (Box 90, Folder Project 191)
  - Stern MBA Commencement Video 1997 Master (Reel 1) (Box 90, Folder Project 191)
  - Commencement 1994 (Reel 1) (Box 90, Folder Project 192)
  - NYU on the Air 1999 (Reel 1-9), 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder Project 193)
  - Americorps Events; Training (Reel 1-37), 1994-1997 (Box 91, Folder Project 194)
  - Stern Centennial Celebration Dinner (Reel 1-4), 1999 (Box 91, Folder Project 195)
  - Wagner Comptroller Event (Reel 1-15), 1999 (Box 92, Folder Project 196)
  - Ray Kelly Press Conference at NYU, 1994 (Box 92, Folder Project 198)
  - South Korean President Kim at NYU (Reel 1-3), 1995 (Box 92, Folder Project 199)
  - Mignonette Yin Cheng (Non-NYU Project), 1995 (Box 92, Folder Project 200)
  - Highlights from 1948 Games NYU vs. Manhattan and Colorodo featuring Ray Lumpp (Reel 1) (Box 92, Folder Project 201)
  - Michelangelo Statue Found (Reel 1-3), undated (Box 92, Folder Project 202)
  - Oliva on Charlie Rose (Reel 1-4), 1993 (Box 92, Folder Project 203)
  - Virtual College for SCE (Reel 1), undated (Box 92, Folder Project 204)
  - Wagner Recruitment Video (Reel 1-30, 32-36), 1995 (Box 93, Folder Project 205)
  - Musical Theater Hall of Fame: Jerry Herman Salute (Reel 1-6), 1999 (Box 93, Folder Project 206)
  - Racism on Campus: Students Speak Out (Reel 1), undated (Box 94, Folder Project 207)
  - Commencement 1999 (Reel 4-24), cuid18365 (Box 94, Betacam sp Project 208)
    Duration: 30 minutes
  - Commencement 1999 Master (Reel 1) (Box 94, Folder Project 208)
  - Commencement 1999 (B-roll Tape), May 13, 1999; cuid18366 (Box Shared University Archives 140, Betacam sp Project 208)
  - Shiseido Endowment to Grey Art Gallery (Reel 1), 1999 (Box 95, Folder Project 210)
  - Shiseido Endowment to Grey Art Gallery Master (Reel 1), 1999 (Box 95, Folder Project 210)
  - Vice President Al Gore at Law School (Reel 1-3), 1999 (Box 95, Folder Project 211)
  - L. Jay Oliva Interview (Reel 1-2), 1995 (Box 95, Folder Project 212)
  - Global Law School Summit in Florence, Italy - Highlights (Reel 21-33), 2000 (Box 96, Folder Project 213)
  - Wagner - Metal Health Services in NYC: Lessons from the Andrew Goldstein Case (Reel 1-4), 2000 (Box 96, Folder Project 214)
  - Stern UG Recruitment Video (Reel 1-6, 9, 10, 13, 16-20, 22-26), 1999 (Box 96, Folder Project 214)
  - NYU Phonathon B-Roll (Reel 1-2), 2000 (Box 96, Folder Project 216)
  - College of Dentistry 1990 Graduation (Reel 1) (Box 96, Folder Project 217)
  - America's Education Revolution (Reel 1), 1993 (Box 96, Folder Project 218)
  - Marty Brest, Oliver Stone Hot Dogs for Gaugin-Brest, The Madman of Martinique-Stone (Reel 1), undated (Box 96, Folder Project 219)
  - Picasso Would Have Made a Glorious Waiter (Reel 1), undated (Box 96, Folder Project 220)
  - Filmmakers: The Next Generation (Reel 1), undated (Box 97, Folder Project 221)
  - UG Entry into the University of Cambridge (Reel 1), undated (Box 97, Folder Project 222)
  - New York University (Reel 1), undated (Box 97, Folder Project 223)
  - NYU TV Showcase (Reel 1), 1985 (Box 97, Folder Project 224)
  - The Miracle at Washington Square (Reel 1-2), undated (Box 97, Folder Project 225)
  - Progressive Governance Summit (Reel 1-2), undated (Box 97, Folder Project 227)
  - Stern UG CD-ROM Video Update (Reel 17, 19, 20), 2000 (Box 97, Folder Project 229)
  - NYU Online (Reel 1-32), 1999-2000 (Box 98, Folder Project 231)
  - School of Law Video 2000 (Reel 4-8) (Box 98, Folder Project 232)
  - Irish Sing-A-Long (Reel 1-4), 2000 (Box 98, Folder Project 233)
  - Distinguished Teaching Medal 2000 (Reel 21 - 25) (Box 99, Folder Project 234)
  - NYU in the News 2000 (Reel 10,22), 1999-2000 (Box 99, Folder Project 235)
  - Stern UG Pre-Commencement Video 1999 (Reel 1-14, 17-20) (Box 99, Folder Project 236)
  - TSOA Salute 2000 (Reel 1-14) (Box 100, Folder Project 237)
  - TSOA Salute 2000 Master (Reel 1) (Box 100, Folder Project 237)
  - Michael Kayne Recital (Reel 1-3), 2000 (Box 100, Folder Project 238)
  - Grey Art Gallery / Shiseido Makeup Video (Reel 1-16), 2000 (Box 100, Folder Project 239)
  - Dental VNR for Kelly Bourdierd (Reel 1), 2000 (Box 100, Folder Project 240)
  - Stern MBA Alumni Lecture with Mary Farrell (Reel 1-2), 2000 (Box 100, Folder Project 241)
  - "Hostage", undated (Box 100, Folder Project 242)
  - Shiseido Advertisement Compilation (Reel 1-2), 1960-1991 (Box 101, Folder Project 244)
  - Shiseido Advertisement Compilation Master(Reel 1), 2000 (Box 101, Folder Project 244)
  - Grad Alley 2000 (Reel1 1 - 3) (Box 101, Folder Project 245)
  - Commencement 2000 (Reel 1-14) (Box 101, Folder Project 246)
  - Commencement 2000 Master (Reel 1) (Box 101, Folder Project 246)
    - Shiseido Stills Master (Reel 1-3), nd (Box 101, Folder Project 250)
  - Shiseido Stills (Reel 1, 4-6), undated (Box 101, Folder Project 250)
  - C-Team Cabaret and Auction 2000 (Reel 1-4) (Box 101, Folder Project 251)
  - Reprographic Services Video (Reel 1-11), 2000 (Box 102, Folder Project 253)
  - UG Admissions Website (Reel 1-6), 2000 (Box 102, Folder Project 255)
  - Alumni Video 2000 (Reel 1-3, 7-14) (Box 102, Folder Project 256)
    - Ken Langone Interview, November 14, 2000; cuid18676 (Box 102, Betacam sp Reel 14)
      Duration: 18 minutes
  - Stern Langone Program Orientation (Reel 1-8, 15-19, 23, 25, 53), 2000 (Box 102, Folder Project 257)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2001 (Reel 1-22, 24) (Box 103, Folder Project 259)
  - Stern UG Pre-Commencement Ceremony 2000 (Reel 1-2) (Box 103, Folder Project 262)
  - D. Koehler Birthday Video (Reel 1-10), undated (Box 103, Folder Project 263)
  - NYU Online Oral Cancer Screening (Reel 1-4), 2000 (Box 104, Folder Project 264)
  - Jane Brody Acceptance Speech (Reel 1), 2000 (Box 104, Folder Project 265)
  - Jane Brody Acceptance Speech Master (Reel 1), 2000 (Box 104, Folder Project 265)
  - American Cancer Society/NYU Dental School - Oral Cancer PSA (Reel 1-6), 2000 (Box 104, Folder Project 266)
  - TISCH 35th Anniversary Gala (Reel 1-32), 2000 (Box 104, Folder Project 267)
  - Autumn Fest 2000 (Reel 1-3) (Box 104, Folder Project 268)
  - Debra James Memorial (Reel 1-7, 10), 2000 (Box 105, Folder Project 270)
  - Stern Community Service (Reel 1-3, 9,10), 2000 (Box 105, Folder Project 271)
  - Casa Italiana 10th Anniversary Dinner (Reel 1-3), 2000 (Box 105, Folder Project 275)
  - Stern UG Recruitment Video Update (Reel 1-2, 5, 7, 8, 11-17, 20), 2001 (Box 105, Folder Project 276)
  - Kimmel Center Video (Project 278), 2000-2001; cuid19071
    - Reel 1 -- Dr. Oliva Interview, December 15, 2000 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 1)
    - Reel 2 -- Margot Marshak Interview, December 15, 2000 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 2)
    - Reel 3 -- Jib Shots of Architectural Model, December 15, 2000 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 3)
    - Reel 4 -- Kevin Roche Interview, Tape 1 of 2, December 18, 2000; cuid19072 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 4)
      Duration: 29 min
    - Reel 5 -- Kevin Roche Interview, Tape 2 of 2 / Kimmel Model B-Roll, December 18, 2000; cuid19073 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 5)
      Duration: 31 min
    - Reel 6 -- Kimmel Model B-Roll of Dining Area, December 18, 2000 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 6)
    - Reel 7 -- Paintings of Theatre, undated (Box 106, Cd Reel 7)
    - Reel 8 -- Kimmel Interview, January 12, 2001 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 8)
    - Reel 9 -- Farrah Pepper Interview, January 12, 2001 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 9)
    - Reel 10 -- Master for Florida Event, February 3, 2001 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 10)
    - Reel 11 -- Protection Master for Florida Event, February 3, 2001 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 11)
    - Reel 12 -- Michael Harrington Interview, January 26, 2001 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 12)
    - Reel 13 -- Animation Final Version, undated (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 13)
    - Reel 14 -- Animation, World Trade Center Darker, undated (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 14)
    - Reel 15 -- Animation, Not Final, undated (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 15)
    - Reel 16 -- Dr. Oliva Interview (Audio of Reel 1), December 15, 2000 (Box 106, Audiocassette Reel 16)
    - Reel 17 -- Margot Marshak Interview (Audio of Reel 2), December 15, 2000 (Box 106, Audiocassette Reel 17)
    - Reel 18 -- Kevin Roche Interview (Audio of Reel 4), December 18, 2000; cuid19075 (Box 106, Audiocassette Reel 18)
    - Reel 19 -- Kevin Roche Interview (Audio of Reel 5), December 18, 2000; cuid19074 (Box 106, Audiocassette Reel 19)
    - Reel 20 -- Kimmel Interview (Audio of Reel 8), January 12, 2001 (Box 106, Audiocassette Reel 20)
    - Reel 21 -- Farrah Pepper Interview (Audio of Reel 9), January 12, 2001 (Box 106, Audiocassette Reel 21)
    - Reel 22 -- Michael Harrington Interview (Audio of Reel 12), January 26, 2001 (Box 106, Audiocassette Reel 22)
    - Reel 23 -- Blueprints of Kimmel Center B-Roll, January 11, 2001 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 23)
    - Reel 24 -- Kimmel Center Animation without World Trade Center, October 9, 2001 (Box 106, Betacam sp Reel 24)
  - NYU on the Air 2001 (Reel 1-6) (Box 106, Folder Project 278)
  - Law School New Building Photos (Reels 11-18, 32) (Box 107, Folder Project 283)
  - Animation Frames, undated, 2001 (Box 107, Folder Project 283)
  - Law School New Building Audio (Reel 37-42) (Box 107, Folder Project 283)
  - Law School New Building Interviews and Animation (Reel 1-10, 20-21, 25-34, 45), 2001 (Box 107, Folder Project 283)
  - Stern Langone Program Orientation Spring 2001 (Reel 1-6) (Box 107, Folder Project 285)
  - Stern CEO Series-Tom Murphy of Cap Cities (Reel 1-6), 1995 (Box 108, Folder Project 286)
  - Stern CEO Series-Tom Murphy of Cap Cities Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 108, Folder Project 286)
  - Meet the CEOs-Management Style - Highlights Master (Reel 1-2), undated (Box 108, Folder Project 287)
  - Stern CEO Series-Goldstein of Unilever (Reel 1-5), 1996 (Box 108, Folder Project 288)
  - Stern CEO Series-Goldstein of Unilever Master (Reel 1), 1996 (Box 108, Folder Project 288)
  - Leadership Conference Graphics (Reel 1-2), 2001 (Box 108, Folder Project 289)
  - Stern CEO Series-Philip J. Carroll of Shell Oil (Reel 1-4), 1996 (Box 108, Folder Project 291)
  - Stern CEO Series-Philip J. Carroll of Shell Oil Master (Reel 1), 1996 (Box 108, Folder Project 291)
  - Stern CEO Series-Augustine (Reel 1-6), undated (Box 108, Folder Project 292)
  - Stern CEO Series-Augustine Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 108, Folder Project 292)
  - Dental School-Video Clips for Lobby and Hall Monitors (Reel 1-2), undated (Box 109, Folder Project 305)
  - Rector's Conference 2001 (Reel 1-28) (Box 109, Folder Project 308)
  - TSOA Salute 2001 (Reel 1-5), 1999-2001 (Box 109, Folder Project 309)
  - Guys and Dolls (Reel 1-13), 2001 (Box 110, Folder Project 310)
  - ITS Video (Reel 1-4), 2001 (Box 110, Folder Project 311)
  - ITS Video Master (Reel 1), 2001 (Box 110, Folder Project 311)
  - Brennan Center Video (Reel 1-35, 37-43), 2001 (Box 111, Folder Project 314)
  - Brennan Center Video Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 111, Folder Project 314)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards 2001 (Reel 1-4, 6-15, 23, 26-29) (Box 112, Folder Project 315)
  - Vilar Scholars Luncheon (Reel 1-2), 2001 (Box 112, Folder Project 316)
  - SOE Spring 2001 Recital Series Presents Michael Harrington (Reel 1-3) (Box 112, Folder Project 319)
  - Commencement 2001(Reel 1-13) (Box 112, Folder Project 320)
  - TISCH Calling Card Video (Reel 1-5), 2002 (Box 113, Folder Project 322)
  - NYU Online I-author Demonstration (Reel 1), 2001 (Box 113, Folder Project 323)
  - Wagner Website (Reel 1-6), 2001 (Box 113, Folder Project 324)
  - Stern UG Parents' Weekend 2001 (Reel 1-16) (Box 113, Folder Project 325)
  - World Trade Center Reaction (Reel 1-5), 2001 (Box 113, Folder Project 328)
  - Law School Online Course Video (Reel 1), 2001 (Box 114, Folder Project 329)
  - Jennifer Goode Recital (Reel 1-3), 1999 (Box 114, Folder Project 330)
  - Casey Hushion Recital (Reel 1-2), 1999 (Box 114, Folder Project 331)
  - Law School Groundbreaking Ceremony (Reel 1-2), 2001 (Box 114, Folder Project 332)
  - NYU Family Gathering (Reel 1-2), 2001 (Box 114, Folder Project 333)
  - Stern UG Recruitment Video 2002 (Reel 1-26), 2001-2002 (Box 114, Folder Project 334)
  - Alumni Website (Reel 1-2), 2002 (Box 114, Folder Project 335)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2002 (Reel 1-19) (Box 115, Folder Project 336)
  - William J. Clinton Dialogue-Islam and America in a Global World Panel 1-4 Master (Reel 1-5), 2002 (Box 115, Folder Project 337)
  - William J. Clinton Dialogue-Islam and America in a Global World Pane 4 Master (Reel 6), 2002 (Box 116, Folder Project 337)
  - William J. Clinton Dialogue-Islam and America in a Global World (Reel 1-17), 2002 (Box 116, Folder Project 337)
  - NYU on the Air 2002 (Reel 1-13) (Box 117, Folder Project 338)
  - NYU Trustees' Trip to Florence and Madrid (Reel 1-4), undated (Box 117, Folder Project 339)
  - President Oliva Tribute Video (Reel 1-16), 2002 (Box 117, Folder Project 340)
  - Weinfeld Gala 2002 (Reel 1-17) (Box 118, Folder Project 341)
  - 30 Years at Gallatin-A Celebration (Reel 1-4), 2002 (Box 118, Folder Project 342)
  - A Party for L. Jay Oliva (Reel 1-3), 2002 (Box 118, Folder Project 343)
  - Grossinger/Alda Event (Reel 1-3), 2002 (Box 119, Folder Project 347)
  - Stern UG Pre-Commencement Video 2002 (1-16) (Box 119, Folder Project 348)
  - Dean Sexton Portrait Unveiling-April 25,2002 (Reel 1) (Box 119, Folder Project 349)
  - Alumni Dinner (Reel 1-5), 2002 (Box 120, Folder Project 350)
  - Dean Daly Tribute Video (Reel 1-7, 8-28), 2002 (Box 120, Folder Project 351)
  - Dean Daly Tribute Video Master (Reel 1-4), 2002 (Box 120, Folder Project 351)
  - Commencement 2002 (Reel 1-8) (Box 120, Folder Project 352)
  - Image Presentations' Stern UG Recruitment Video (Reel 1), undated (Box 121, Folder Project 353)
  - Law School CD-ROM/Video (Reel 1-2), 2002 (Box 121, Folder Project 354)
  - The Leadership University for the New Millennium-With Credits (Reel 1-6, 9, 11, 13-15, 18, 19, 22-26), 2002 (Box 121, Folder Project 356)
  - Trustee Inductee Dinner (Reel 1-11), 2002 (Box 121, Folder Project 357)
  - Stern UG Parents' Weekend 2002 (Reel 1-9) (Box 122, Folder Project 358)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2003 (Reel 1-18, 21-36) (Box 122, Folder Project 359)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2003 (Reel 37-71, 73) (Box 123, Folder Project 359)
  - Rector's Conference 2002 (Reel 1-22) (Box 124, Folder Project 362)
  - John Sexton Installation Ceremony (Reel 1-8), 2002 (Box 124, Folder Project 363)
  - John Sexton Installation Gala (Reel 1-3), 2002 (Box 124, Folder Project 364)
  - Gallatin: On the Cutting Edge (Reel 1-4), 2002 (Box 124, Folder Project 366)
  - Gallatin: Alternative Conference (Reel 1-3), 2002 (Box 124, Folder Project 367)
  - September 11th Remembrance Ceremony (Reel 1-5), 2002 (Box 125, Folder Project 369)
  - Gallatin 30th Anniversary Video (Reel 1-22), 2003 (Box 125, Folder Project 374)
  - Gallatin Video/CD-ROM Project (Reel 1-4), 2003 (Box 125, Folder Project 374)
  - Gallatin 30th Anniversary Video Master (Reel 1-2), 2003 (Box 125, Folder Project 374)
  - NYU Student Experience (Reel 7,17,18, 45-48, 63, 65, 88, 89, 91-93), 2003 (Box 125, Folder Project 375)
  - NYU Student Experience (Reel 1-4, 8-16, 21-44, 49-51), 2003 (Box 126, Folder Project 375)
  - NYU Student Experience (Reel 52-62, 67-87), 2003 (Box 127, Folder Project 375)
  - Commencement 2003 (Reel 1-11) (Box 128, Folder Project 376)
  - Alumni Weekend 2003 (Reel 1-10) (Box 128, Folder Project 380)
  - Stern MBA Recruitment Video-2003 (Reel 8- 9) (Box 128, Folder Project 381)
  - Niall Ferguson Acceptance Speech (Reel 1), 2003 (Box 128, Folder Project 382)
  - Gallatin Anniversary Gala (Reel 1-6), 2003 (Box 128, Folder Project 383)
  - Pre-Commencement Breakfast 2003 (Reel 1-2) (Box 128, Folder Project 384)
  - Law CD-ROM 2003 (Reel 1-3, 7-9) (Box 128, Folder Project 385)
  - SCPS-Ethical Decision Making Course (Reel 2), 2003 (Box 128, Folder Project 386)
  - Gallatin Cd-Rom (Reel 3-18), 2003 (Box 129, Folder Project 388)
  - Photo Bureau Services Video (Reels 2, 4, 6), undated (Box 129, Folder Project 392)
  - Clinton Visits Stern MBA for Harlem Business Initiative Presentation (Reel 1-3), 2003 (Box 129, Folder Project 394)
  - Tisch Gala 2003 (Reel 1-2) (Box 129, Folder Project 395)
  - Alumni Magazine Discussion Groups (Reel 1-22), 2003 (Box 129, Folder Project 397)
  - Dental School Media Training (Reel 1), 2004 (Box 129, Folder Project 399)
  - CEO Lecture Series with Tom Freston (Reel 1-3), 2004 (Box 129, Folder Project 400)
  - Stern UG Recruitment Video 2004 (Reel 1-14, 16, 18-26, 30, 32-34) (Box 130, Folder Project 406)
  - Ireland House Documentary (Reel 7), 2004 (Box 130, Folder Project 407)
  - Dean Choi Tribute Video (Reel 1-2), 2004 (Box 130, Folder Project 413)
  - Dean Message to Stern Alumni (Reel 1), 2004 (Box 130, Folder Project 415)
  - Law CD-ROM 2004 (Reel 1-8, 15,17,31) (Box 130, Folder Project 416)
  - TSOA Gala Los Angeles 2004 (Reels 1-8, 10-17) (Box 130, Folder Project 431)
  - Dental School Website (Reels 2-14), 2005 (Box 131, Folder Project 435)
  - Bob Tisch Tribute Video (Reel 1-7, 9-26, 29), 2005 (Box 131, Folder Project 436)
    - Interview with Bob Tisch (tape 1 of 2), 2002 March 12; 1 Betacam_SP (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 37, Box 131, Folder Project 436)
      Original Format: BetacamSP Color/ Sound TRT: 00:30:00
    - Interview with Bob Tisch (tape 2 of 2), 2002 March 12; 1 Betacam_SP (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 38, Box 131, Folder Project 436)
      Original Format: Betamax Color/ Sound TRT: 00:23:00
  - Bob Tisch Tribute Video Master (Reel 1-2), 2005 (Box 131, Folder Project 436)
  - Bob Tisch Tribute Video Audio Tapes (Reel 1-3), 2005 (Box 131, Folder Project 436)
  - Senator John Kerry on Late Show with David Letterman (Reel 1), 2004 (Box 132, Folder Project 437)
  - ADA Conference on Bioterrorism Preparedness (Reel 1-3), 2005 (Box 132, Folder Project 438)
  - Diversity Focus Groups (Reel 1-8), 2005 (Box 132, Folder Project 446)
  - Video Tribute to Naomi Levine (Reel 1-22, 24-26, 29-69), 2005 (Box 132, Folder Project 456)
  - Dental Hygiene Recruitment Video (Reel 1-12), 2005 (Box 133, Folder Project 442)
  - NYU Website Videos (reels 1-14, 17-27), 2006 (Box 133, Folder Project 457)
  - TSOA Gala 2005 (Reel 1-2) (Box 133, Folder Project 461)
  - NYU Dental School - Kevin Paulino's Anodontia Procedure (Reel 1), 2005 (Box 133, Folder Project 462)
  - Dean Alfano's Nursing Award Acceptance Speech (Reels 1-2), 2005 (Box 133, Folder Project 464)
  - Naomi Levine Tribute Dinner for the Bronfman Center (Reel 1-5), 2005; cuid17544 (Box 133, Folder Project 466)
    Duration: Reel 1: 29 minutes; Reel 2: 31 minutes; Reel 3: 31 minutes; Reel 4: 32 minutes; Reel 5: 9 minutes
  - Medical School Faces Video (Reel 1-5), undated (Box 133, Folder Project 486)
  - Medical School Cochlear Implant Video (Reel 1), undated (Box 133, Folder Project 488)
  - Timothy Higdon's Class (Reel 2-6, 8, 11), 2006 (Box 133, Folder Project 505)
  - Naomi Levine's Seminar on Philanthropy (Reel 4-10, 18-25, 34), 2001 (Box 134, Folder Project 318)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 27, 88, 90, 261, 273, 274, 284), undated (Box 134, Folder Project 0226)
  - Wagner stills disk, undated (Box 134, Folder Project 0226)
  - Wagner Georgetown stills (Disk 2), undated (Box 134, Folder Project 0226)
  - Wagner Georgetown stills (Disk 3), undated (Box 134, Folder Project 0226)
  - Wagner interview with Chris McNickle (12.15.00 #1), undated (Box 134, Cassette Project 0226)
  - Wagner (Doc 6200 #3), undated (Box 134, Cassette Project 0226)
  - Robert F. Wagner, Jr., with Rudolph Giuliani (06.001.1.1055) (2 of 2 only), undated (Box 134, Cassette Project 0226)
  - Kenneth Jackson NTV (Beta #1), 5 December 2000 (Box 134, Cassette Project 0226)
  - Robert F. Wagner interview (06.002.1.6000), 5 May 1976 (Box 134, Cassette Project 0226)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (V.5), undated (Box 134, Disc Project 0226)
    Length: 30 minutes
  - Naomi Levine's Seminar on Philanthropy (Reel 1-3, 11-17, 26-33), 2001 (Box 135, Folder Project 318)
  - Ireland House Dedication (Reel 12), 1993 (Box 136, Folder Project 43)
  - Wagner Graduate School of Public Service (Reel 1-4, 5-9, 18, 30-32), 1990 (Box 136, Folder Project 54)
  - Wagner Graduate School of Public Service Master (Reel 1), 1990 (Box 136, Folder Project 54)
  - Admissions Video (Reel 1-8, 11-15, 19-26, 28-34, 37-39, 41-50, 66-67), 1997 (Box 137, Folder Project 82)
  - Admissions Video (Reel 51-57, 61, 63, 66-71, 84, 86, 94, 96-99, 102-105, 107, 112, 115-119), 1997 (Box 138, Folder Project 82)
  - Wagner Recruitment Video (Reel 31), undated (Box 138, Folder Project 205)